const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "4.3",
    title: "A lot of, a few, many, much",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "trochę kawy",
    back: "a little coffee",
  },
  {
    front: "trochę czasu",
    back: "a little time",
  },
  {
    front: "trochę piasku",
    back: "a little sand"
  },
  {
    front: "dużo kawy",
    back: "a lot of coffee",
  },
  {
    front: "dużo czasu",
    back: "a lot of time",
  },
  {
    front: "dużo piasku",
    back: "a lot of sand",
  },
  {
    front: "kilka książek",
    back: "a few books",
  },
  {
    front: "kilku przyjaciół",
    back: "a few friends",
  },
  {
    front: "kilka domów",
    back: "a few houses",
  },
  {
    front: "wiele książek",
    back: "many books/ a lot of books",
  },
  {
    front: "wielu przyjaciół",
    back: "many friends/ a lot of friends",
  },
  {
    front: "wiele domów",
    back: "many houses/ a lot of houses",
  },
  {
    front: "W misce jest trochę zupy.",
    back: "There is a little soup in the bowl.",
  },
  {
    front: "Potrzebuję trochę czasu.",
    back: "I need a little time.",
  },
  {
    front: "Cz możesz dodać trochę cukru?",
    back: "Can you add a little sugar?",
  },
  {
    front: "Piję dużo wody.",
    back: "I drink a lot of water.",
  },
  {
    front: "Ona spędza dużo czasu z przyjaciółmi.",
    back: "She spends a lot of time with her friends.",
  },
  {
    front: "W ogrodzie jest dużo miejsca.",
    back: "There is a lot of space in the garden.",
  },
  {
    front: "Kupiłem kilka nowych książek.",
    back: "I bought a few new books.",
  },
  {
    front: "Podróżuję z kilkoma przyjaciółmi.",
    back: "I travel with a few friends.",
  },
  {
    front: "Na naszej ulicy jest kilka dużych domów.",
    back: "There are a few big houses on our street.",
  },
  {
    front: "Mam wiele książek na mojej półce.",
    back: "I have many books on my bookshelf./ I have a lot of books on my bookshelf.",
  },
  {
    front: "Mają wielu przyjaciół.",
    back: "They have many friends. / They a lot of friends.",
  },
  {
    front: "W kolejce jest dużo ludzi.",
    back: "There are many people in the queue. / There are a lot of people in the queue.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie zostało dużo mleka.",
    back: "There's not much milk left.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie mam dużo czasu.",
    back: "I don't have much time.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie potrzebujemy dużo pieniędzy.",
    back: "We don't need much money.",
  },
  {
    front: "Nie mam wielu przyjaciół.",
    back: "I don't have many friends.",
  },
  {
    front: "W tej okolicy nie ma wielu domów.",
    back: "There aren't many houses in this area.",
  },
  {
    front: "Niewiele osób przyszło na imprezę.",
    back: "Not many people came to the party.",
  },
];
export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
